{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269646915","data":{"timestamp":" 947269646915"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_1"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269692394","data":{"timestamp":" 947269692394"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269694624","data":{"timestamp":" 947269694624"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269696963","data":{"timestamp":" 947269696963"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269699235","data":{"timestamp":" 947269699235"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269701532","data":{"timestamp":" 947269701532"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_3"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 1"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269750133","data":{"timestamp":" 947269750133"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269752311","data":{"timestamp":" 947269752311"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 1"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269754736","data":{"timestamp":" 947269754736"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269794846","data":{"timestamp":" 947269794846"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" pic"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" page_5"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269794901","data":{"timestamp":" 947269794901"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUSABABISHA"," userResponse":" HUSABABISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269825740","data":{"timestamp":" 947269825740"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" c6937123-b210-4275-a1a8-060a591ad89e"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269825788","data":{"timestamp":" 947269825788"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" 459ebf69-130b-431a-bc34-2728d065a2e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HILO"," userResponse":" HILO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.pic.hear::story_44","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269861796","data":{"timestamp":" 947269861796"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" 459ebf69-130b-431a-bc34-2728d065a2e9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Nani husababisha hilo kutendeka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947269861861","data":{"timestamp":" 947269861860"," userId":" 5B13001421"," sessionId":" 5B13001421_20000107_212629"," gameId":" 7262a807-c634-4495-b73a-befb1efe3c53"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_questions"," tutorId":" story.pic.hear__story_44"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Maziwa ndani ya kikombe- moto sana moto sana."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIKOMBE"," userResponse":" KIKOMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}